criminaldefenselawyer.com 2007-07-23

# Criminal Defense Lawyer - Attorney for your Criminal Defense Case - Privacy Policy Lawyers Attorneys

Your Privacy is important to us at CriminalDefenselawyer.com. CriminalDefenselawyer.com LLC has adopted information management guidelines that define our customer and advertiser relationships. These guidelines disclose the privacy policies for the entire CriminalDefenseLawyer.com group of Web sites and functioning URLs including state, regional, and national sites. Since Internet technologies are rapidly evolving underlying business models are evolving. Accordingly, guidelines may change. Any changes will be posted here. 

CriminalDefenseLawyer.com is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of Web sites to which it may link. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure: CriminalDefenseLawyer.com will not sell or rent your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information to anyone. 

CriminalDefenseLawyer.com will only send your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 

We have your consent to share the information; We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; We need to send the information to companies or third-parties who work on behalf of CriminalDefenseLawyer.com to provide a product or service to you; We are required to provide such information to respond to subpoenas, court orders or other legal process; or We find that your actions on our web sites violate the General Site Agreement or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

Security: CriminalDefenseLawyer.com takes every precaution to protect our Users' information. Your CriminalDefenseLawyer.com registration information is password-protected for your privacy and security.

While using the PleaseAdvise or any other service, you may be asked to enter sensitive information. That information is transmitted to a secure server and is protected with encryption. 

IP Addresses: CriminalDefenseLawyer.com also logs IP addresses for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. (Your IP address indicates the location of your computer on the Internet.) We do not log IP addresses to track your session, nor do we link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. 

Credit Card Information: If you use a credit card to pay for a CriminalDefenseLawyer.com listing, etc., we will continue to charge your account pursuant to the terms of the contract, unless otherwise agreed to in writing, or until cancellation is effected pursuant to the terms of the contract. If you give us credit card information for any other purpose or to pay for any other type of purchase, it will be used one time only to fulfill one order, and CriminalDefenseLawyer.com will not store your credit card information. 

Cookies: "Cookies" give users a special, random ID that are small text files, which are stored on the hard drive of a user's computer. CriminalDefenseLawyer.com employs cookies to recognize you and your access privileges for certain locations on the CriminalDefenseLawyer.com sites, such as the Practice Centers, as well as to track site usage. Subscribers who do not accept cookies from the CriminalDefenseLawyer.com sites cannot access many areas of CriminalDefenseLawyer.com's group of Web sites. For detailed information about our use of cookies, please contact us using our hyperlink. We use an advertising server developed by a third party, to display ads on our site. Some of these ads may contain cookies that are set by third parties (i.e., advertising agencies or advertising clients). We do not have access to these cookies or any information that they may contain. 

Links to other web sites: This web site contains links to other sites, which may or may not collect cookies. CriminalDefenseLawyer.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website. 

Site and Service Updates: We also may send you site and service announcements or updates. You are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the website or CriminalDefenselawyer.comcom services. We may communicate with you to provide requested services and discuss your registration via email or phone. 

Changing or Deleting Your Information and Preferences: You can make most changes yourself through your Account Management page at any time. You may request removal or deletion of your CriminalDefenseLawyer.com registration information by sending an email to [info@swidigital.com](mailto:luciano@swidigital.com?subject=medicalmalpractice.com&body=)

Changes: CriminalDefenseLawyer.com may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time at its discretion.  
Any changes will be posted in this section 

TOP OF THE PAGE

Find a Lawyer
